Could this be leading to…?
這個發展該不會…
I broke up with her.
我跟她分手了
I want to go somewhere private.
我想要去能兩人獨處的地方
Is it okay to make a mistake with me?
即使跟我發生什麼也沒關係？
Sorry. The bathroom had a line.
抱歉，廁所好多人
Oh. It's fine.
喔，沒關係
It was a sexless relationship.
原因是沒有性生活
What?
什麼？
That's why we broke up.
我們分手的原因
I see.
這樣啊
Yeah.
對了
Kosaka, are you uncomfortable talking about stuff like this?
香坂，你不喜歡聽這種話題吧？
I just wanted to talk to someone about it.
我只是想和人說說話而已
No, it's fine.
不會，沒關係的
Go ahead.
你願意的話就和我說吧
I can't usually hear about other people's sex lives.
一般人不會提起的性生活
I want to know.
我想要知道
Well…
嗯…
I'm not sure where to start.
要從哪裡開始說好呢？
I'm probably asexual.
我有可能是無性戀
Asexual?
無性戀？
I can have romantic feelings for someone, but I have no sexual desires.
雖然對別人會有戀愛感情 但是沒有性衝動
I think it was around puberty…
大概是在青春期的時候吧…
Everyone was reading dirty magazines, but I had no interest whatsoever.
周圍的人都在看色情書刊 但我卻完全沒有興趣
Honestly, I didn't like them.
不如說我不喜歡那些
I did my best and slept with her a few times.
我也努力和女友試了好幾次
But something kept feeling off.
但怎麼樣都覺得很怪
Then I found out about asexuality online and thought, "Oh, that's me."
然後我在網路上知道無性戀後 “喔，這不就是我嗎？”
I wasn't the only one.
原來不只有我啊？
Hey.
我說
Let's do it.
來做吧？
Sorry.
抱歉
I'm feeling tired today.
我今天很累
Some other time.
下次再說吧
"Some other time"?
下次是什麼時候？
What?
什麼？
I'm always the one asking, and you keep turning me down.
每次都是我來求你 然後每次都被拒絕
Don't you get how miserable it makes me?
你知道我這樣有多可悲嗎？
I really loved her, but…
我真的很喜歡她，但是…
I felt bad.
感覺很對不起她
And…
而且…
I didn't think we could ever have closed it.
我覺得我們不可能彌補的
Huh?
什麼？
The gap between us.
我們之間的鴻溝
Nowadays there are all types of people.
不過現在也有各式各樣的人
I might have a chance with someone like me.
說不定能遇見和我一樣的人
So I haven't given up.
所以我也沒那麼慘啦
To think he'd have the exact opposite problem.
想不到竟然是和我完全相反的煩惱
Everyone has their own thing, I guess.
真的是有各式各樣的人呢
Sorry. I got drunk and might have said too much.
抱歉，我好像喝太多 說了很多有的沒的
No, not at all.
沒有，不會啦
I was the one who told you to.
是我叫你說的嘛
You know I was raised overseas.
我是在國外長大的
And hugging is common over there.
在國外擁抱很平常吧？
Uh, right.
嗯，對啊
So, can I hug you?
所以，要不要抱一下？
A wholesome one.
沒有別的意思
Wait, are you drunk?
等等，你喝醉了吧？
As a colleague and a friend.
用同期同事和朋友的身分
A pure and clean hug.
來個清爽單純的擁抱吧
Okay.
好啊
I wonder why…
到底是為什麼呢？
When I like physical touch like this…
我明明很喜歡這樣的肢體接觸的…
Yeah.
的確
It must be amazing to have someone to touch in this way.
如果能有一個像這樣 撫摸我的人在身邊，會很幸福吧？
Seriously…
搞什麼？
Who wrote this draft?
這份草稿是誰寫的？
I did. Is there something…
是我，有什麼…
His name is Hashigodaka not Kuchitaka!
他的名字是 像梯子的“髙”不是口的“高”
How can you get the name wrong? Are you a rookie?
連人名都會搞錯，你是菜鳥嗎？
Oh… I am sorry.
真的很抱歉
Hey.
我說你
What do you think makes work possible?
你覺得工作是建立在什麼基礎上？
It's trust. Trust!
是信任，信任關係！
Everything can collapse in an instant.
信任破產只是眨眼間的事情
Are you okay?
你還好嗎？
Yeah, I'm fine.
嗯，我還好
I'm the one who messed up.
是我這邊不好
I'm home.
我回來了
Come on.
真是的
You could've given her a bath.
你至少先幫她洗澡啊
Yeah.
好
You're late, Mom.
媽媽好慢喔
Sorry. I'll make dinner now.
抱歉，我馬上準備晚餐
Thanks for the follow. What has it been, 13 years?
謝謝追蹤，13年沒見面了吧？
Hmm?
怎麼了？
Oh, nothing.
喔，沒什麼
Wait, it's really you?
咦？是本人嗎？
I was surprised to see you got serialized.
連載很厲害耶，我好驚訝
How about you? Are you still drawing manga?
菜菜你呢？還有在畫漫畫嗎？
Yeah, I self-publish.
嗯，同人活動之類的
I see, that's great.
這樣啊，太好了
I might be receiving the next Sosho Art Manga Award.
我之後可能會拿到創書藝術漫畫獎
It's a lot of pressure.
感覺壓力好大
What is it?
怎麼了？
It's nothing.
沒事
The Sosho Art Manga Award…
創書藝術漫畫獎…
That's amazing.
好厲害
The gap keeps getting wider…
差距越來越大了…
Hmm? Something's definite--
怎麼了？果然還是…
I said it's nothing!
我就說沒什麼了！
I found another place that looks good.
我找到另一間不錯的店
A sheep bar?
羊酒吧？
Also! Aren't you doing nothing but drink recently?
話說，你最近除了喝酒外 都沒別的事做了嗎？
Ouch.
說中了
Huh?
怎麼了？
What?
什麼？
Has something happened?
發生什麼事了嗎？
Oh, no.
喔，沒有
I just read manga until late last night.
我只是昨天看漫畫看到很晚
Was it Kakuta's new one?
在看角田老師的新作嗎？
No.
不是
Someone I know.
是熟人的作品
What? You know a professional artist?
什麼？你認識專業的漫畫家嗎？
That's cool.
好酷喔
Does your husband read them too?
是話說你老公也會看嗎？
Mangas?
漫畫嗎？
Not at all.
他完全不看
He understands the appeal but isn't interested.
他雖然能理解，但完全沒興趣
I see.
這樣啊
Then what prompted you?
那契機是什麼啊？
Huh?
什麼？
To date, and marry your husband.
你和老公交往結婚的契機
Who asks something like that?
你要問這個喔？
It's so good.
好好吃喔
You really like these, don't you?
你真的很喜歡這個呢
Is your stomach acting up?
你肚子痛嗎？
Is there a toilet around here?
這附近的廁所在哪？
This is so embarrassing.
好丟臉啊
Right in the middle of a date…
在約會的時候…
I'm sorry.
抱歉
Huh?
怎麼了？
Nana the glutton.
貪吃鬼菜菜
How fun.
好有趣
It was fun.
很開心呢
Whenever I was with him.
跟老公在一起的時候
Fun.
很開心？
Oh no. Why am I thinking about Kagiya?
天啊，為什麼我會想到鍵谷？
I get it.
我懂
You do?
是嗎？
ENERGY PARTNERS
（活力夥伴）
Oh.
啊
You're…
你是之前的…
Kosaka.
我是香坂
Are you on your way home from work?
你剛下班要回家嗎？
Yes.
對
The station is this way, isn't it?
車站是往這邊嗎？
Oh, no.
啊，不是
I'm dropping by somewhere on the way.
我今天稍微繞了點路
There's a retro game-café I frequent close to here.
這附近有一間 我常去的復古遊戲喫茶店
Retro games? Do you play with your friends?
復古遊戲？跟朋友一起玩嗎？
No.
不是
By myself.
我自已一個人
By yourself…
一個人…
Um!
那個
Can I come with you?
我可以一起去嗎？
What?
什麼？
DENKIYA HALL
（電氣屋廳堂）
Wow! It's really Pac-Man!
哇，真的是《小精靈》耶
Will you be getting the usual iced coffee?
老樣子點冰咖啡嗎？
Yes.
對
I'll have the same.
那我也一樣
Um, does this actually work?
那個，這個真的可以玩嗎？
It does.
可以
You're so good at it!
好強
The ghosts can't get you at all.
幽靈完全追不到你呢
I played it quite a bit at one point.
我有一陣子很沉迷
It's embarrassing.
真是難為情
No, it's impressive.
不會，很厲害
I know you don't get this good by just doing it casually.
只是隨便亂玩的話不會這麼強的
Would you like to try?
你要玩玩看嗎？
Yes.
好啊
That's the first time I've seen his face.
第一次看到他的臉
Good night.
晚安
Is Dad not coming home yet?
爸爸還不回家嗎？
No.
還沒呢
I'm home.
我回來了
Welcome back.
你回來了
Hide, about what happened yesterday…
阿秀，昨天的事情…
I'll put these in here.
我把這個放這裡喔
Huh?
什麼？
You like these, don't you, Mom?
媽媽喜歡這個吧？
Uh, yeah.
呃，對
This one is for Hina.
這個是給日奈的
Um…
那個…
Are you not mad about yesterday?
昨天的事，你沒生氣嗎？
Yesterday?
昨天？
Oh. I forgot.
喔，我忘記了
Is it strawberry? I want it!
是草莓口味嗎？我要吃！
Not now. After dinner.
不行，要等晚餐之後
You need a bath first.
而且你還要先洗澡
Let's eat them.
來吃吧
Huh?
咦？
Let's have them now.
我們現在吃吧
Thank you.
謝謝
Hmm?
嗯？
For what?
謝什麼？
Well…
嗯…
Everything.
很多事情
I was all over the place just a moment ago,
剛剛還心煩意亂的
but Hidenao made me feel so much better.
但多虧秀直讓我感覺好多了
I'm so simple.
真是單純
But that's who I am.
但這就是我呢
What's going on?
怎麼了啊？
And stop calling me "Mom."
話說別再用“媽媽”叫我了
That's for Hina to do.
那是日奈在叫的
Oh, um, what was the name of the red ghost again?
那個，你說紅色的幽靈叫什麼？
Pinky-inky?
平奇、英奇
And…
還有…
It's Blinky.
布林奇
You remembered it well.
你記得很熟呢
He smiled.
他笑了
Oh.
喔
Let me do it.
交換一下
It's warm.
好溫暖
WE'RE HAVING YAKISOBA TODAY
（今天吃炒麵喔）
I'm home.
我回來了
Welcome home.
歡迎回來
You should've gone ahead and eaten.
你先吃也沒關係啊
I didn't want to eat alone.
自己吃也太寂寞了吧？
Is it good?
好吃嗎？
Yeah.
嗯
You're working overtime a lot lately.
你最近很常加班呢
Are you okay?
你還好嗎？
What do you mean?
你是指什麼？
I mean, your body.
身體之類的
Oh. Yeah, my body is fine.
喔，身體沒事
The stress is what's bad.
但是壓力大到不行
What?
怎麼說？
The young ones are so useless.
年輕人真的很沒用
They leave on the dot even if they still have work to do.
工作都還沒完成 卻這麼放著然後準時回家
It's unbelievable.
真是不敢相信
Working too hard doesn't seem to be trendy these days.
畢竟現在已經不流行拼命工作了
That's not my point.
我不是在說這個
If you don't want to be there
不僅沒有幹勁
and you're no help, then just quit already.
也派不上用場，不如早早辭職算了
They get paid for nothing.
薪水小偷啊
What?
幹嘛？
Nothing.
沒什麼
What about you?
你呢？
You're home early a lot lately.
你最近都很早回來
Yeah, I finished the big project.
對，剛完成一個大專案
Oh.
對了
Take a look at this.
你看這個
It's coming out next week.
下週開賣
Miyuki.
美由紀
I'm tired.
我很累
I would rather spend that time sleeping.
有做的時間不如拿來睡覺
You can dash by eating cookies…
吃掉餅乾後可以衝刺…
Oh, you're right!
喔，真的耶
It's the flavor of adulthood.
這是大人的味道
Next time you can have some too, Hina.
日奈下次也可以試試看
It's our 10th year living together.
同居第十年
Makoto is gentle and calm.
沉著冷靜的真
I didn't realize it at the time.
這時候，我並沒注意到
That I was taking this happiness for granted.
我認為這種幸福理所當然
That was close.
好可惜
That was Blinky.
剛剛那是布林奇
That one was Blinky.
那就是布林奇啊
Would you like to go for dinner together?
你不介意的話 下次要不要一起吃飯？
She kept saying we'd work hard together, but quit right away.
她總是說我們一起努力 結果結婚後卻馬上辭職了
Um.
那個
I've never been in a woman's home before. I'm a little nervous.
我第一次到女生家裡，有點緊張
I want to touch him.
我想碰碰他
Right now, that's all.
現在大概…這樣就好